AFL-CIO Railway Employees' Department Records 5478
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series XVI: Federal Affairs - Consolidation, Retirements, Pensions, ICC, Waterways, Ex Parte 171, Emergency Railway Legislation, etc., 1928-1970
  - Application for Relief from the Requirements of Ex Parte 171 - A-G, 1961-1964 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    Code No. 35-127; Nov. 15, 1961 - Mar. 11, 1964
  - Application for Relief from the Requirements of Ex Parte 171 - E-I, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    Code No. 35-127; Jul. 13, 1959 - Dec. 2, 1960
  - Application for Relief from the Requirements of Ex Parte 171, 1957-1960 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    Code No. 35-127; Feb. 15, 1957 - Dec. 22, 1960
  - Application for Relief from the Requirements of Ex Parte 171, 1959-1960 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    Code No. 35-127; Oct. 2, 1959 - Jan. 30, 1960
  - Six Hour Day Investigation, 1932 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    Code No. 35-132; Feb. 1, 1932 - Dec. 20, 1932
  - Six Hour Day Investigation, 1933-1934 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    Code No. 35-132, pt. 2; Jan. 9, 1933 - Dec. 28, 1934
  - Interstate Commerce Commission - General, 1931-1960 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    Code No. 35-133, pt. 1; Jan. 21, 1931 - Dec. 14, 1960; Includes appropriations for ICC
  - Interstate Commerce Commission - General, 1961-1965 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    Code No. 35-133, pt. 2; Jan. 16, 1961 - Dec. 3, 1965; Includes appropriations for ICC
  - Uniform System of Bankruptcy, 1932-1939 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    Code No. 35-135, pt. 1; May 3, 1932 - Dec. 18, 1939
  - Revenue Bill Tax, 1932-1943 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    Code No. 35-136, pt. 1; Mar. 17, 1932 - Aug. 25, 1943
  - Revenue Bill Tax, 1943-1947 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    Code No. 35-136, pt. 2; Sept. 3, 1943 - Dec. 4, 1947
  - Federal and State Unemployment Insurance, 1928-1936 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    Code No. 35-141; Nov. 3, 1928 - Dec. 14, 1936
  - Industrial Recovery Bill, 1932-1937 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    Code No. 35-152; May 18, 1932 - Aug. 25, 1937
  - Industrial Recovery Bill, 1940-1970 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    Code No. 35-152, pt. 2; Jan. 12, 1940 - Dec. 23, 1970
  - Public Documents, etc. on Industrial Recovery Act, 1933 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    Code No. 35-152-A, pt. 1; Jun. 20, 1933 - Aug. 2, 1933
  - Establishment of National Labor Relations Act, 1934-1940 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    Code No. 35-152-B, pt. 1; Apr. 9, 1934 - Aug. 19, 1940
  - Establishment of National Labor Relations Act, 1941-1946 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    Code No. 35-152-B, pt. 2; Jan. 27, 1941 - Dec. 18, 1946
  - National Labor Relations Act, 1947 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    Code No. 35-152-B, pt. 3; Jan. 20, 1947 - Jul. 3, 1947
  - National Labor Relations Act and Taft-Hartley Law, 1947-1952 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    Code No. 35-152-B, pt. 4; Jun. 30, 1947 - Jul. 3, 1952
  - National Labor Relations Act, 1953-1962 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    Code No. 35-152-B, pt. 5; Feb. 3, 1953 - Jun. 28, 1962
  - Emergency Railroad Legislation, 1933 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    Code No. 35-153, pt. 1; Mar. 15, 1933 - Jun. 30, 1933
  - Emergency Railroad Legislation, 1933 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    Code No. 35-153, pt. 2; Jul. 1, 1933 - Aug. 11, 1933
  - Emergency Railroad Legislation, 1933 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    Code No. 35-153, pt. 3; Aug. 11, 1933 - Aug. 29, 1933
  - Emergency Railroad Legislation, 1933-1934 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    Code No. 35-153, pt. 4; Aug. 30, 1933 - Feb. 1, 1934
  - Emergency Railroad Legislation, 1934-1935 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    Code No. 35-153, pt. 5; Jan. 24, 1934 - Dec. 12, 1935
  - Emergency Railroad Legislation - Documents, etc. issued by Federal Coordinator, 1933 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    Code No. 35-153-A, pt. 1; Jul. 10, 1933 - Sept. 20, 1933
  - Emergency Railroad Legislation - Documents, etc. issued by Federal Coordinator, 1933 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    Code No. 35-153-A, pt. 2; Sept. 9, 1933 - Nov. 6, 1933
  - Emergency Railroad Legislation - Documents, etc. issued by Federal Coordinator, 1933-1934 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    Code No. 35-153-A, pt. 3; Nov. 8, 1933 - Apr. 9, 1934
  - Emergency Railroad Legislation - Documents, etc. issued by Federal Coordinator, 1934 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    Code No. 35-153-A, pt. 4; Feb. 1, 1934 - Nov. 7, 1934
  - Emergency Railroad Legislation - Documents, etc. issued by Federal Coordinator, 1934-1935 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    Code No. 35-153-A, pt. 5; Nov. 13, 1934 - May 24, 1935
  - Emergency Railroad Legislation - Reports, 1935 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    Code No. 35-153-A, pt. 6; Jun. 3, 1935 - Jul. 29, 1935
  - Reports and Documents, 1935-1936 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    Code No. 35-153-A, pt. 7; Aug. 7, 1935 - Jun. 8, 1936
  - Reports and Documents, 1936-1940 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    Code No. 35-153-A, pt. 8; Jun. 11, 1936 - Jun. 3, 1940
  - First Report of Federal Coordinator of Transportation on Transportation Legislation, 1934 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    Code No. 35-153-A; Jan. 20, 1934
  - Second Report of Federal Coordinator of Transportation on Transportation Legislation, 1934 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    Code No. 35-153-A; Mar. 10, 1934
  - Fourth Report of Federal Coordinator of Transportation on Transportation Legislation, 1936 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    Code No. 35-153-A; Jan. 21, 1936
  - Final Report - "Comparative Labor Standards in Transportation", 1937 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    Code No. 35-153-A; Mar. 1937
- Series XVII: National Railroad Adjustment Board - Legislation, Correspondence, Reports, Minutes, Etc., 1933-1970
  Correspondence (carbons and originals), publications, circulars, minutes, reports, awards, petitions, exhibits, and clippings regarding discussion of National Railroad Adjustment Board (NRAB) - filing procedures, individual representation before the Board
  - Legislation - General, 1933-1938 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    Code No. 35-158, pt. 1; Nov. 13, 1933 - Dec. 8, 1938
  - National Railroad Adjustment Boards, 1934 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    Code No. 35-166-General, pt. 1; Feb. 1, 1934 - Dec. 28, 1934
  - National Railroad Adjustment Boards, 1934-1939 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    Code No. 35-166-General, pt. 2; Dec. 28, 1934 - Aug. 31, 1939
  - National Railroad Adjustment Boards, 1939-1940 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    Code No. 35-166-General, pt. 3; Aug. 30, 1939 - Feb. 25, 1940
  - National Railroad Adjustment Boards, 1940 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    Code No. 35-166-General, pt. 4; Mar. 4, 1940 - Oct. 30, 1940
  - National Railroad Adjustment Boards, 1940-1945 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    Code No. 35-166-General, pt. 5; Oct. 31, 1940 - Jul. 25, 1945
  - National Railroad Adjustment Boards, 1945-1947 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    Code No. 35-166-General, pt. 6; Jul. 31, 1945 - Aug. 19, 1947
  - National Railroad Adjustment Boards, 1947-1963 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    Code No. 35-166-General, pt. 7; Aug. 25, 1947 - Jun. 26, 1963
  - National Railroad Adjustment Boards - Notices from RLEA members of railroads who have refused to apply decisions, 1935-1942 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    Code No. 35-166-B, pt. 1; Sept. 16, 1935 - Dec. 14, 1942
  - Failure to apply awards, 1945-1953 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    Code No. 35-166-B, pt. 2; Oct. 4, 1945 - Jun. 30, 1953
  - Failure to apply awards, 1953-1961 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    Code No. 35-166-B, pt. 3; Aug. 5, 1953 - Apr. 24, 1961
  - Appointment of Labor Members to National Railroad Adjustment Board, 1934-1941 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    Code No. 35-166-C, pt. 1; Jun. 19, 1934 - Dec. 31, 1941
  - Appointment of Labor Members to National Railroad Adjustment Board, 1942-1954 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    Code No. 35-166-C, pt. 2; Oct. 16, 1961 - Nov. 15, 1965
  - National Railroad Adjustment Boards - Special Board of Adjustments, 1961-1965 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    Code No. 35-166-D, pt. 1; Oct. 16, 1961 - Nov. 15, 1965
  - National Railroad Adjustment Boards - Correspondence re Index-Digest of Awards of the 2nd Division, 1934-1938 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    Code No. 35-166-2, pt. 1; Aug. 20, 1934 - Nov. 30, 1938
  - National Railroad Adjustment Boards - Correspondence re Index-Digest of Awards of the 2nd Division, 1938-1943 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    Code No. 35-166-2, pt. 2; Dec. 1, 1938 - Dec. 13, 1943
  - National Railroad Adjustment Boards, 1942-1956 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    Code No. 35-166-2, pt. 3; Dec. 2, 1942 - Dec. 20, 1956
  - National Railroad Adjustment Boards, 1957-1958 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    Code No. 35-166-2, pt. 4; Jan. 23, 1957 - Dec. 24, 1958
  - Minutes of Section 2 only, 1934-1940 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    Code No. 35-166-2-Minutes, pt. 1; Dec. 11, 1934 - Feb. 26, 1940
  - Minutes of Section 2 only, 1940-1941 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    Code No. 35-166-2-Minutes, pt. 2; Mar. 5, 1940 - Dec. 19, 1941
  - Minutes of Section 2 only, 1942-1944 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    Code No. 35-166-2-Minutes, pt. 3; Jan. 5, 1942 - Jul. 7, 1944
  - Minutes of Section 2 only, 1944-1947 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    Code No. 35-166-2-Minutes, pt. 4; Jul. 6, 1944 - Mar. 31, 1947
  - Minutes of Section 2 only, 1947-1949 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    Code No. 35-166-2-Minutes, pt. 5; Apr. 1, 1947 - Jun. 30, 1949
  - Minutes of Section 2 only, 1949-1951 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    Code No. 35-166-2-Minutes, pt. 6; Jul. 5, 1949 - Dec. 20, 1951
  - Orders and Bound Volumes, 1945-1949 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    Code No. 35-166-2-O&BV, pt. 8; Jan. 2, 1945 - Jul. 21, 1949
  - Orders and Bound Volumes, 1949-1954 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    Code No. 35-166-2-O&BV, pt. 9; Jul. 27, 1949 - Oct. 21, 1954
  - Orders and Bound Volumes, 1954-1966 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    Code No. 35-166-2-O&BV, pt. 10; Nov. 1, 1954 - Apr. 20, 1966
  - Third Division, 1935-1960 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    Code No. 35-166-3, pt. 1; Apr. 2, 1935 - Jun. 30, 1960
  - National Railroad Adjustment Boards - Submissions in Dispute, 1960-1961 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    Code No. 35-166-3, pt. 2; Jul. 13, 1960 - Feb. 28, 1961
  - National Railroad Adjustment Boards - Submissions in Dispute, 1961 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    Code No. 35-166-3, pt. 3; Mar. 8, 1961 - May 24, 1961
  - National Railroad Adjustment Boards - Submissions in Dispute, 1961 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    Code No. 35-166-3, pt. 4; May 25, 1961 - Jun. 16, 1961
  - National Railroad Adjustment Boards - Submissions in Dispute, 1961 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    Code No. 35-166-3, pt. 5; Jun. 23, 1961 - Jan. 20, 1961
  - National Railroad Adjustment Boards - Submissions in Dispute, 1962 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    Code No. 35-166-3, pt. 6; Jan. 15, 1962 - May 25, 1962
  - National Railroad Adjustment Boards - Submissions in Dispute, 1962 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    Code No. 35-166-3, pt. 7; Jun. 4, 1962 - Nov. 21, 1962
  - National Railroad Adjustment Boards - Submissions in Dispute, 1963 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    Code No. 35-166-3, pt. 8; Jan. 4, 1963 - Sept. 30, 1963
  - National Railroad Adjustment Boards - Submissions in Dispute, 1963-1964 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    Code No. 35-166-3, pt. 9; Jun. 26, 1963 - Sept. 28, 1964
  - National Railroad Adjustment Boards - Submissions in Dispute, 1964-1965 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    Code No. 35-166-3, pt. 10; Oct. 1, 1964 - Dec. 3, 1965
  - National Railroad Adjustment Boards - Submissions in Dispute, 1966-1970 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    Code No. 35-166-3, pt. 11; Jan. 18, 1966 - Dec. 17, 1970
  - Awards #301-364, 1936-1937 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    Code No. 35-166-3A; Sept. 29, 1936 - Feb. 8, 1937
  - Submissions in Dispute, 1938-1961 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    Code No. 35-166-4, pt. 1; Jul. 27, 1938 - Apr. 25, 1961
  - Submissions in Dispute, 1961-1965 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    Code No. 35-166-4, pt. 2; Jun. 12, 1961 - Mar. 19, 1965
  - Legislative Representative - Section 2, 1934-1946 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    Code No. 35-171; Sept. 11, 1934 - Dec. 31, 1946
  - Legislative Representative, 1947-1950 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    Code No. 35-171, pt. 3; Jan. 2, 1947 - May 23, 1950
  - Legislative Representative, 1950-1952 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    Code No. 35-171, pt. 4; Jun. 1, 1950 - Dec. 31, 1952
  - Department of Labor - General, 1935-1940 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    Code No. 35-176, pt. 1; Jan. 15, 1935 - Dec. 10, 1940
  - Department of Labor - General, 1941-1946 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    Code No. 35-176, pt. 2; Jan. 6, 1941 - Oct. 31, 1946
  - Labor Advisory Committee-Bureau of Labor Statistics and Joint Trade Union Advisory Comm. On International Affairs, 1946-1948 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    Code No. 35-176-C, pt. 1; Dec. 4, 1946 - Jan. 9, 1948
  - Committees of Bureau of Labor Statistics, 1965-1966 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    Code No. 35-176-C, pt. 9; May 3, 1965 - Apr. 7, 1966
  - National Planning Association, 1942-1965 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    Code No. 35-180, pt. 1; Nov. 12, 1942 - Jan. 3, 1965
  - Social Security, 1935-1947 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    Code No. 25-204, pt. 1; Aug. 15, 1935 - Dec. 4, 1947
  - Social Security, 1948-1961 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    Code No. 35-204, pt. 2; Feb. 17, 1948 - Apr. 24, 1961
  - Social Security, 1961-1965 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    Code No. 35-204, pt. 3; May 1, 1961 - Apr. 20, 1965
  - Social Security, 1936 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    Code No. 35-204A, pt. 1; Mar. 5, 1936 - Nov. 25, 1936
  - Social Security, 1936-1938 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    Code No. 35-204A, pt. 2; Dec. 1, 2936 - Oct. 3, 1938
  - Housing Legislation, 1934-1965 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    Code No. 35-209, pt. 1; Jun. 8, 1934 - Feb. 26, 1965
  - Consolidation of Railroads - Employee Protection Legislation, 1934-1936 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    Code No. 35-216, pt. 1; Oct. 24, 1934 - Apr. 30, 1936
  - Washington Job Protection Agreement, 1936 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    Code No. 35-216, pt. 2; May 1, 1936 - Dec. 30, 1936
  - Railroads participating in agreements for co-ordination of facilities, 1919-1949 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    Code No. 35-216, pt. 3; Jul. 8, 1919 - Aug. 10, 1949
  - Washington Job Protection, 1949-1958 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    Code No. 35-216, pt. 4; Sept. 15, 1949 - May 27, 1958
  - Washington Job Protection, 1958-1963 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Code No. 35-216, pt. 5; Jul. 9, 1958 - Aug. 14, 1963
  - Washington Agreement - Consolidation of Texas and New Orleans Railroad, and Southern Pacific Railroad, 1938-1940 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Code No. 35-216-2; Sept. 14, 1938 - Jul. 30, 1940
  - Tennessee Valley Authority, 1940-1956 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    Code No. 35-221, pt. 1; Jan. 12, 1940 - Nov. 1, 1956
- Series XXX: Railroad Unemployment Insurance
  - Railroad Unemployment Insurance, 1935-1938 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    Code No. 35-235; Dec. 23, 1935 - Apr. 19, 1938
  - Railroad Unemployment Insurance, 1938 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    Code No. 35-235, pt. 2; Apr. 19, 1938 - Oct. 31, 1938
  - Railroad Unemployment Insurance, 1938-1939 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    Code No. 35-235, pt. 3; Nov. 1, 1938 - Dec. 28, 1939
  - Railroad Unemployment Insurance, 1940-1941 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    Code No. 35-235, pt. 4; Jan. 2, 1940 - Dec. 19, 1941
  - Railroad Unemployment Insurance, 1942-1946 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    Code No. 35-235, pt. 5; Jan. 5, 1942 - Aug. 27, 1946
  - Railroad Unemployment Insurance, 1946-1950 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    Code No. 35-235, pt. 6; Sept. 9, 1946 0 Aug. 22, 1950
  - Railroad Unemployment Insurance, 1950-1954 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    Code No. 35-235, pt. 7; Oct. 24, 1950 - May 24, 1954
  - Railroad Unemployment Insurance, 1954-1955 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    Code No. 35-235, pt. 8; Jun. 5, 1954 - Dec. 30, 1955
  - Railroad Unemployment Insurance, 1956-1959 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    Code No. 35-235, pt. 9; Jan. 11, 1956 - Apr. 17, 1959
  - Railroad Unemployment Insurance, 1959-1961 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    Code No. 35-235, pt. 10; May 4, 1959 - Dec. 28, 1961
  - Railroad Unemployment Insurance, 1962-1964 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    Code No. 35-235, pt. 11; Jan. 10, 1962 - Dec. 21, 1964
  - Railroad Unemployment Insurance - Comm., 1939-1940 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    Code No. 35-235, Comm., pt. 1; Nov. 6, 1939 - Dec. 5, 1940
  - Railroad Unemployment Insurance - Comm., 1941-1944 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    Code No. 35-235, Comm., pt. 2; Feb. 14, 1941 - Apr. 24, 1944
- Series XXXI: Fair Labor Standards Act
  - Fair Labor Standards Act, 1937-1939 (Box 72a, Folder 1)
    Code No. 35-240, pt. 1; Jun. 7, 1937 - Jul. 27, 1939
  - Fair Labor Standards Act - Comm., 1939-1941 (Box 72a, Folder 2)
    Code No. 35-240, Comm.; pt. 1; Dec. 5, 1939 - Aug. 15, 1941
  - Fair Labor Standards Act, 1939-1940 (Box 72a, Folder 3)
    Code No. 35-240, pt. 2; Aug. 11, 1939 - Dec. 1940
  - Fair Labor Standards Act, 1941-1945 (Box 72a, Folder 4)
    Code No. 35-240, pt. 3; Jan. 1941 - Dec. 1945
  - Reorganization of Government Agencies other than ICC, 1933-1949 (Box 72a, Folder 5)
    Code No. 35-247; Apr. 20, 1933 - Jun. 27, 1949
  - Pipeline Construction in re National Defense, 1939-1941 (Box 72b, Folder 1)
    Code No. 35-270, pt. 1; Jan. 12, 1939 - May 28, 1941
  - Transportation Act of 1939 (Box 72b, Folder 2)
    Code No. 25-285, pt. 1
  - Transportation Act of 1939, 1955-1961 (Box 72b, Folder 3)
    Code No. 25-285, pt. 1; Mar. 8, 1955 - Apr. 3, 1961
  - Transportation Act of 1940 (Box 72b, Folder 4)
    Code No. 35-285, pt. 2
  - National Transportation Policy, 1961-1963 (Box 72b, Folder 5)
    Code No. 25-385, pt. 2; Jul. 19, 1961 - Mar. 26, 1963
  - Transportation Act of 1940, 1942 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    Code No. 35-285, Comm., pt. 1; Jan. 16, 1942 - Dec. 8, 1942
  - Transportation Act of 1940, 1941-1954 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    Code No. 35-285, pt. 3; Jan. 9, 1941 - Feb. 19, 1954
- Series XVIII: Consolidations, Mergers, Reorganizations and Abandonments, 1938-1970
  Correspondence (carbons and originals), minutes, circulars, clippings, agreements, reports, statistical data, and legislative and legal materials regarding legislative proposals to improve passenger train service; discussion of the Urban Mass Transit Act
  - Consolidation, Abandonments and Reorganization of Railroads, 1939-1958 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    Code No. 35-311; Dec. 4, 1939 - Jul. 9, 1958
  - Consolidation and Abandonments, 1958-1959 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    Code No. 35-311, pt. 2; Jul. 13, 1958 - Dec. 8, 1959
  - Railway Labor Executives Association Files, 1960-1961 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    Code No. 35-311, pt. 3; Jan. 12, 1960 - May 29, 1961
  - Railway Labor Executives Association Files, 1961-1962 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    Code No. 35-311, pt. 4; Jun. 1, 1961 - Jun. 26, 1962
  - Railway Labor Executives Association Files, 1962-1964 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    Code No. 35-311, pt. 5; Jul. 2, 1962 - May 24, 1964
  - Railway Labor Executives Association Files, 1964-1966 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    Code No. 35-311, pt. 6; Jun. 4, 1964 - Mar. 30, 1966
  - Railway Labor Executives Association Files, 1966 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    Code No. 35-311, pt. 7; Apr. 1, 1966 - Sept. 27, 1966
  - Railway Labor Executives Association Files, 1966-1967 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    Code No. 35-311, pt. 8; Oct. 6, 1966 - Apr. 21, 1967
  - Railway Labor Executives Association Files, 1967-1969 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    Code No. 35-311, pt. 9; May 2, 1967 - Dec. 30, 1969
  - Reorganization and Consolidation - Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railway and Chicago, Rock Island and Gulf Railway, 1935-1941 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    Code No. 35-311-7, pt. 1; Aug. 30, 1935 - Nov. 7, 1941
  - Abandonment and Reorganization-Minneapolis and St. Louis Railroad, 1934-1936 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    Code No. 35-311-29, pt. 1; Nov. 20, 1934
  - Abandonment and Reorganization-Minneapolis and St. Louis Railroad, 1937-1940 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    Code No. 35-311-29, pt. 2; Jan. 1, 1937 - Dec. 9, 1940
  - Consolidation - Colorado and Southern Railroad - Ft. Worth and Denver City Railroad - Wichita Valley, 1939-1940 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    Code No. 35-311-50, pt. 1; Jul. 10, 1939 - Dec. 24, 1940
  - Reorganization - Florida East Coast Railroad, 1944-1959 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    Code No. 35-311-251; Nov. 24, 1944 - Dec. 30, 1959
  - Reorganization - Florida East Coast Railroad, 1960-1966 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    Code No. 35-311-251, pt. 2; Jan. 12, 1960 - Apr. 20, 1966
  - Consolidation - New Orleans Terminal, 1938-1947 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    Code No. 35-311-351, pt. 1; Jul. 12, 1938 - Dec. 22, 1947
  - Consolidation - New Orleans Terminal, 1948-1951 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    Code No. 35-311-351, pt. 2; Jan. 14, 1948 - Dec. 12, 1951
  - Consolidation - New Orleans Terminal, 1952-1955 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    Code No. 35-311-351, pt. 2; Jan. 16, 1952 - Dec. 5, 1955
  - Louisville and Nashville Railroad, et. al., Merger, 1960-1961 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    Code No. 35-311-1090, pt. 2; Jan. 12, 1960 - Aug. 30, 1961
  - Norfolk and Western Virginian Railway - Merger, 1959-1960 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    Code No. 35-311-1627, pt. 1; Mar. 19, 1959 - Aug. 30, 1960
  - Norfolk and Western Virginian Railway - Merger, 1960-1961 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    Code No. 35-311-1627, pt. 2; Sept. 1, 1960 - Sept. 28, 1961
  - Norfolk and Western Virginian Railway - Merger, 1961-1963 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    Code No. 35-311-1627, pt. 3; Oct. 2, 1961 - Aug. 27, 1963
  - Chesapeake and Ohio Railway - Control - Baltimore and Ohio Railway, 1960-1963 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    Code No. 35-311-1836, pt. 1; Jun. 16, 1960 - Mar. 26, 1963
  - Chesapeake and Ohio Railway and Baltimore and Ohio Railway - Coordinations, 1963-1970 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    Code No. 35-311-1836, pt. 2; Apr. 1, 1963 - Dec. 31, 1970
  - Seaboard Airline Railroad - Merger - Atlantic Coast Line Railroad, 1958-1961 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    Code No. 35-322-1857, pt. 1; Oct. 1, 1958 - Oct. 31, 1961
  - Seaboard Airline Railroad - Merger - Atlantic Coast Line Railroad, 1961-1963 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    Code No. 35-311-1857, pt. 2; Nov. 1, 1961 - Dec. 24, 1963
  - Seaboard Airline Railroad - Merger - Atlantic Coast Line Railroad, 1964-1966 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    Code no. 35-311-1857, pt. 3; Jan. 2, 1964 - Dec. 21, 1966
  - Seaboard Airline Railroad - Merger - Atlantic Coast Line Railroad, 1967 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    Code no. 35-311-1857, pt. 4; Jan. 3, 1967 - Dec. 28, 1967
  - Seaboard Airline Railroad - Merger - Atlantic Coast Line Railroad, 1967-1968 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    Code no. 35-311-1857, pt. 5; Aug. 26, 1967 - Dec. 23, 1968
  - Southern Pacific Railroad - Control - Western Pacific Railroad, 1960-1964 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    Code No. 35-311-1907, pt. 1; Oct. 13, 1960 - May 15, 1964
  - Southern Railway - Control - Central of Georgia Railroad, 1961-1963 (Box 77, Folder 8)
    Code No. 35-311-1954; Jan. 4, 1961 - Sept. 25, 1963
  - Southern Railway - Control - Central of Georgia Railroad, 1963-1964 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    Code No. 35-311-1954, pt. 2; Oct. 2, 1963 - May 25, 1964
  - Southern Railway - Control - Central of Georgia Railroad, 1964-1966 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    Code No. 35-311-1954, pt. 3; Jun. 5, 1964, Dec. 8, 1966
  - Great Northern Pacific and Burlington Lines, Inc. - Merger, etc. - Great Northern Railway, 1957-1964 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    Code No. 35-311-1968, pt. 1; Dec. 6, 1957 - Aug. 31, 1964
  - Great Northern Pacific and Burlington Lines, Inc. - Merger, etc. - Great Northern Railway, 1964-1966 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    Code No. 35-311-1968, pt. 2; Sept. 2, 1964 - Apr. 22, 1966
  - Great Northern Pacific and Burlington Lines, Inc. - Merger, etc. - Great Northern Railway, 1966-1968 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    Code No. 35-311-1968, pt. 3; May 1, 1966 - Dec. 6, 1968
  - Great Northern Pacific and Burlington Lines, Inc. - Merger, etc. - Great Northern Railway, 1969 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    Code No. 35-311-1968, pt. 4; Jan. 20, 1969 - Dec. 20, 1969
  - Consolidation - Great Northern, Northern Pacific, Chicago Burlington and Quincy and Spokane, Seattle and Seattle System, 1957-1965 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    Code No. 35-311-1969; Dec. 9, 1957 - Sept. 29, 1965
  - Proposed Merger - Great Northern, Northern Pacific, Chicago Burlington and Quincy and Spokane, Seattle and Seattle System, 1957-1966 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    Code No. 35-311-1970, pt. 1; Dec. 9, 1957 - Apr. 22, 1966
  - Consolidation of Norfolk and Western Nickel Plate and Wabash Railroad, 1961-1965 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    Code No. 35-311-1986, pt. 1; Jan. 17, 1961 - Jun. 14, 1965
  - Buffalo Terminal Coordination - System Federation No. 57 and 100, 1961-1963 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    Code No. 35-311-2110; Nov. 13, 1961 - Dec. 31, 1963
  - Rutland Railway Corp. - Abandonment, 1961-1963 (Box 79, Folder 5)